<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nguyen Thuy Ngoc</title>
    <link>https://ngocntkt.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Nguyen Thuy Ngoc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 16:36:11 +0430</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ngocntkt.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Simulation models for group decision making process</title>
      <link>https://ngocntkt.github.io/projects/simulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 16:36:11 +0430</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ngocntkt.github.io/projects/simulation/</guid>
      <description>The motivation behind exploiting simulation experiments is that while a user study is useful and important to understand whether a recommendation model is effective and well-accepted by users, the study itself is yet adequate to fully assess the model performance in numerous potential group situations, given the dynamics of group decision making process.
Our first proposed simulation model of a group discussion has been used to study the impact of alternative combinations of long-term and session-based preferences on the recommendation performance in different group scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Tyrol Suggests for Groups (STSGroup)</title>
      <link>https://ngocntkt.github.io/projects/stsgroup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 16:36:11 +0430</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ngocntkt.github.io/projects/stsgroup/</guid>
      <description>The developed system is called &amp;ldquo;South Tyrol Suggests for Groups&amp;rdquo; (STSGroup) featuring a chat-based interface. Basically, the system enables group members to join a chat environment where they can express opinions through messages, POI proposals and evaluations. Based on the group members&amp;rsquo; actions, the system then tries to provide them with new group recommendations and choice suggestions.
The whole idea behind the chat-based interface design is to support the group discussion process by fostering communication between group members instead of only focusing on negotiation mechanisms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>